<record xmlns="http://www.openarchives.org/OAI/2.0/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><header><identifier>oai:quod.lib.umich.edu:IC-WCL1IC-X-566%5DWCL000669</identifier><datestamp>2020-01-30T01:06:54Z</datestamp><setSpec>dlpsimages:wcl1ic</setSpec><setSpec>dlps:wcl1ic</setSpec></header><metadata><oai_dc:dc xmlns:oai_dc="http://www.openarchives.org/OAI/2.0/oai_dc/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/dc/terms/" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.openarchives.org/OAI/2.0/oai_dc/ http://www.openarchives.org/OAI/2.0/oai_dc.xsd"><dc:title>Plan of Fort-William-Henry and camp, at Lake George / Will: Eyre, engr.</dc:title><dc:creator>Eyre, William, d. 1764.</dc:creator><dc:subject>Lake George, Battle of, N.Y., 1755--Maps, Manuscript.; Manuscript maps.; Maps shelf.; Brun Guide.; Germain Maps.; Fort William Henry (N.Y.)--Maps, Manuscript.; George, Lake (N.Y. : Lake)--Maps, Manuscript.; New York (State)--Maps, Manuscript.; United States--History--French and Indian War, 1754-1763--Maps, Manuscript.</dc:subject><dc:description>Finished topographical map showing fort and entrenched camp, with detailed description of the position.; Shows direction of attack of French and Indians at Battle of Lake George, September 8, 1755.</dc:description><dc:publisher>William L. Clements Library Image Bank</dc:publisher><dc:identifier>http://name.umdl.umich.edu/IC-WCL1IC-X-566%5DWCL000669</dc:identifier><dc:identifier xsi:type="thumbnail">http://quod.lib.umich.edu/cgi/i/image/api/thumb/wcl1ic/566/WCL000669/!250,250</dc:identifier><dc:identifier>wcl000669</dc:identifier><dc:source>William L. Clements Library; George Sackville Germain papers; Sackville, George Germain, Viscount, 1716-1785</dc:source><dc:language>UND</dc:language><dc:type>image</dc:type><dc:format>jpeg</dc:format><dc:rights>The University of Michigan Library provides access to these materials for educational and research purposes. These materials may be under copyright. If you decide to use any of these materials, you are responsible for making your own legal assessment and securing any necessary permission. If you have questions about the collection, please contact the William L. Clements Library: icwcl1ic-umdl-help@umich.edu. If you have concerns about the inclusion of an item in this collection, please contact Library IT: libraryit-info@umich.edu.</dc:rights><dc:rights>http://quod.lib.umich.edu/t/text/accesspolicy.html</dc:rights></oai_dc:dc></metadata></record>